[
  {
    "question": "Спасибо",
    "answer": "Thank You"
  }, {
  "question": "Привет",
  "answer": "Hello"
}, {
  "question": "Пожалуйста",
  "answer": "You're Welcome"
}, {
  "question": "Программист использовал компьютер.",
  "answer": "The programmer used the computer."
}, {
  "question": "сказать",
  "answer": "To speak"
}, {
  "question": "собака",
  "answer": "Dog"
}, {
  "question": "россиянин",
  "answer": "Russian"
}, {
  "question": "улыбаться",
  "answer": "Smile"
}, {
  "question": "кошка",
  "answer": "Cat"
}, {
  "question": "радость",
  "answer": "Happiness"
}, {
  "question": "Добро пожаловать!",
  "answer": "Welcome"
}, {
  "question": "Как Ваши дела?",
  "answer": "How are you?"
}, {
  "question": "До свидания",
  "answer": "Goodbye"
}, {
  "question": "Удачи!",
  "answer": "Good Luck"
}
]
